Previously, on AMC's The Walking Dead.
《行尸走肉》前情提要
We have people, and weapons.
我们有人手和武器
If we strike first, together, we can beat them.
如果我们联盟  先下手为强  就能打败他们
People will die.
会死人
A lot of people, and not just the Saviors.
会死很多人  不仅是救世军
If we can find another way, we have to.
如果能找到更好的办法  必须找到
Just because you now know how to fight, doesn't mean you should seek one.
知道如何打架  不意味着你应该去找茬
You'll just have to convince Ezekiel to bring The Kingdom to fight.
你只用说服以西结带领神之国反抗
No, this is something I am not a part of.
不  我不想参与这事
Ah, it looks light.
看上去少了
Perhaps you might look again, Gavin.
也许你该再看看  加文
We've met our obligations.
我们履行了义务
God damn it.
该死
Wake it up, kid.
醒醒  孩子
Why does it have to be so early?
为什么非得这么早
Got a lot to do today.
今天有很多事要做
You want to go back to sleep?
你想继续睡觉吗
No way.
不想
You said you wanted to be able to knock your brother
你刚来找我的时候
on his butt when you first came to me.
说想打败你哥哥
That really what you want?
你真想这样吗
Yeah.
是啊
No.
不是
You want to be like your brother.
你想跟你哥哥一样
Yeah?
对吗
Yeah. ?
对
All right.
好吧
Check your feet,
检查你的步法
- 'cause if your feet ain't right -- - Nothing's right.
-如果你的步法错  -一切都错
We were just about to come out to clear the --
我们正打算出去清理...
Where's Morgan?
摩根在哪
- You okay? - Where is Morgan?
-你没事吧  -摩根在哪
Why did Jesus bring Daryl and everyone else to the Kingdom?
为什么耶稣带达里尔和其他人来神之国
They, um...
他们
They wanted to see if we could all start working together on things.
他们想看看我们能不能一起合作
The Saviors are still here.
救世军还在
They're not fighting with the Kingdom, but...
他们没跟神之国打仗  但是
Daryl said they beat them back in Alexandria.
达里尔说他们在亚历山大打败了救世军
Is that true?
是真的吗
That they made a deal with them?
他们达成了协议吗
Is everyone okay?
大家都还好吗
Just tell me if it's true.
告诉我是不是真的
You need to talk to Daryl about that.
你得去问达里尔
You wanted me to keep the whole story about you from everybody.
你让我不告诉所有人你的事
Told me not to say where you were,
让我不说你在哪
and I did what you asked.
我照你的吩咐做了
Daryl didn't find you because of me.
达里尔不是靠我找到你的
And what was said between you and him
你俩之间说的话
was said between you and him.
是你俩的事
I will go with you to Alexandria,
我会跟你去亚历山大
if you want to make the trip...
如果你想去
if you want to talk to him.
如果你想跟他谈
You shouldn't go alone.
你不该一个人去
You found what you wanted, right?
你找到了想要的  对吧
You got away from everyone.
你逃开了所有人
Is it what you wanted?
那是你想要的吗
Was it just too late to get away?
还是太迟  已经没法逃离了
Hey, we can leave for Alexandria right now.
我们现在就能去亚历山大
Right now, if you want to.
如果你想的话
Is there anything I can help you with?
我能帮你什么忙吗
- No. - ?Well, can I just --
-不能  -我能不能
If you don't mind, could I walk back to the cottage with you?
如果你不介意  我可以送你回小屋吗
No!
不行
We have a drop today, but I can miss it.
我们今天要上贡  但我可以不去
I just...
我只是
I'm trying to learn,
我在努力学习
and seeing what you did here, I...
看到了你之前做的事  我...
There were five of them.
有五个行尸
I would just really appreciate it
如果你能让我看看
if you would just...let me see how you do what you do.
你是怎么做到的  我会很感激
No. Go do your drop.
不行  去上贡吧
Okay.
好吧
You may approach, Nabila.
准你上前  娜比拉
I'm fine where I am.
我待在原地就好
Shiva likes you.
希瓦喜欢你
That's what I'm afraid of.
我就怕它喜欢我
Tell me what you found.
告诉我你发现了什么
You're not gonna like it.
你不会喜欢的
I like waiting to hear bad news less.
我更不喜欢被坏消息吊胃口
We got a little problem
我们遇到了个小问题
that could turn into a big problem inside of a week.
但它一周之内就可能变成大问题
Most of the plants down there, they got weevils.
下面大部分植物都生了象鼻虫
We have to cut and burn everything
我们必须把它们全部剪了烧掉
before the weevils get to the main crops in the courtyard.
不然会蔓延到院子里的主要农作物上
I know the Royal Garden is important to you.
我知道皇家花园对你而言很重要
I'm sorry.
很抱歉
Thank you, Nabila.
谢谢你  娜比拉
Do what must be done.
该怎么办就怎么办吧
Here's the beautiful thing, Your Majesty --
陛下  美妙之处就在于...
you can tear it out and cut it down.
你可以把它们拔了剪了
You can burn it and throw it all away.
你可以把它们烧了扔掉
But if you want, it can all grow back.
但如果你想的话  它们还会再长回来
Okay. I think I just pissed myself.
好吧  我觉得我尿裤子了
I'm-a gonna go.
我得走了
We're at "five minutes go."
五分钟后出发
Okay.
好
Thank you for this.
谢谢你给了我这本书
I'm still thinking about it.
我还在思考
"To injure an opponent is to injure oneself."
"伤害敌人就是伤害自己"
Get injured no matter what.
无论如何都会受伤是吧
I got something for you -- for the new place.
我给你带了件礼物  放在你新家的
Thanks.
谢了
I found it at a restaurant I was scavenging.
我出去找物资时在一家餐厅里发现的
I know a girl, and she, uh, fixed it up for me.
我认识一个女孩  她帮我把它修好了
There.
瞧
I was getting tired of looking at that nail.
我正好看那钉子看烦了呢
So, who's the girl?
那个女孩是谁
We're at, like, "three minutes go" right now,
我们还有三分钟就要出发了
so...
所以...
Kid's too young to be a father.
那孩子小小年纪就得当爹
Were you one?
你当过爹吗
I was, thank God.
当过  谢天谢地
But I wasn't too young --
但我那时可不小
perfect age, perfect time.
完美的年纪  完美的时间
I had myself the perfect family and the perfect life.
我有完美的家庭和完美的人生
I didn't ask for much, and I got more than I deserved.
我所求不多  得到的却超过预期
And you?
你呢
I'm sorry for how things have been between you and me.
很抱歉我俩之间有些不快
I think you're wrong about killing...
我觉得你对杀戮的看法是错的
about how you think things can last like this with the Saviors.
觉得我们能和救世军长期共处的想法也是错的
But I'm sorry.
但我还是得道歉
I know you're a good man.
我知道你是个好人
The day's coming where you can't be that good.
但总有一天  你不能再这样好下去
When that happens,
等到那时
don't beat yourself up about it.
别为此自责
Benjamin, it's time for us to take our leave.
本杰明  我们该出发了
See you, little man.
再见  小伙子
Leave the cobbler.
把馅饼放下
Really?
真要这样吗
Jerry.
杰瑞
Fine.
好吧
Who's the girl?
那女孩是谁
Everyone stay down. Get your guns up.
大家都别动  把枪端好
Somebody blocked the road.
有人把路堵上了
Can't be for anything good.
一定不是什么好事
Your Majesty, stay inside.
陛下  留在车里
Take a look if you want,
如果你们想的话就下来看看
but keep your guns up.
但把枪都端好了
Echelon right.
梯队向右
Force towards the building over there.
向那栋楼行进
Let's close around the king.
大家围着国王
I got cover.
我来掩护
Let's move towards the building.
我们到那栋楼去
Benjamin, get your gun up.
本杰明  把枪端起来
Think that's high enough?
端得够高了吗
You're fine, man.
你做得挺好的  伙计
Jesus...
天啊
This world drives one mad.
这个世界把人逼疯了
People have lived through every kind of misery...
人们经历了各种苦难
tyrants, genocide, systems of quiet hate...
暴君  种族灭绝  仇恨制度
while others enjoy freedom on the same piece of land.
而别人却在同一块土地上享受着自由
Yet this, how we must exist now...
然而如今  我们唯有这样生存
It is mere luck we are not all insane.
没全都被逼疯仅仅是走运
It isn't luck, Your Majesty.
这不是走运  陛下
How's that?
怎讲
The world does drive people crazy now.
这世界确实把人逼疯了
But...
但是
you made us another world.
你为我们创造了新世界
You're late.
你们迟到了
If you could indulge us your pardon, our path...
希望你能原谅  我们在路上...
I don't want to hear about it.
我不想听
Don't interrupt the king.
别打断国王
You rat-faced prick.
你个獐头鼠目的混蛋
Ezekiel, there aren't any kings,
以西结  这里没有国王
presidents, or prime ministers.
总统或首相
And all that is a fairy tale, too.
那些都是童话故事了
Don't bring that "Your Highness" Shit our way.
别在我们面前玩"陛下"那一套
Now, I appreciate that you've been delivering, but...
很感谢你们一直上贡  但是
things have been unnecessarily tense,
气氛总是不必要的紧张
and that makes me unnecessarily tense.
所以我也不必要的紧张
I didn't go this route for stress.
我来办这事不是找压力的
No. Just the opposite.
不  我是来放松的
So let's get to it. Do you have today's offering?
那么进入正题  今天的贡品带了吗
I want your guns, too.
你们的枪我也要
We did not agree to that.
协议可没有这条
Well, you got a choice...
你们有个选择
Same one that's been there since the beginning, I guess.
我猜一开始你们就有这个选择
You can give up your guns,
你们可以交出枪
or you can try to use them.
或者开枪试试
What's it gonna be?
选哪个
We should give them over, Your Majesty.
我们应该交枪  陛下
Or maybe I'll just shove this down your throat.
或许我应该用棍子捅穿你喉咙
Give Morgan his stick back.
把棍子还给摩根
Then you can have the guns.
枪就给你们
- And all of us can go on with our day's journeys. - Ezekiel...
-然后大家各奔东西  -以西结
I need you to understand the gravity of what's happening here.
我需要你明白现在这种局面的严重性
I gave you a choice.
我给了你选择
What is it going to be?
你选哪个
Come on.
选吧
You know the answer.
你知道该选哪个
It's fine.
算了
Give them your guns.
枪给他们
We took your guns just now
我们拿走你们的枪
because things are about to get emotional.
是因为你们马上会动感情
You guys have proven
据以往的经验
that you don't do so good with emotional.
你们一感情用事  就搞砸事情
You're short.
贡品不够
We said 12. I count 11.
我们要十二颗  这只有十一颗
There are 12 there.
是十二颗
- There aren't. - Count again.
-不是  -再数一遍
You count them!
你来数
I counted them.
我数过的
I did. T-This is impossible.
我数过  这不可能
It's possible.
有可能
It's real.
是真的
It's happening now.
就发生在眼前
And the problems have to end...now.
而现在  问题必须解决
You have to learn the stakes here,
你们必须明白代价
so we're gonna teach you.
我们得教教你们
You don't have to do anything.
你们不用动手
We'll get you twice the tribute in an hour.
一小时之内我们会送来双倍贡品
Right now...
现在
is the only time that matters.
是唯一重要的时间
And right now...
而现在
you haven't held up your side of the bargain.
你们没有履行义务
After we have talked about things,
在我们谈了
over and over again and again.
一遍又一遍之后
So we're gonna deal with all of this...
我们只能做个了结
right now.
就现在
Right now as in..."right now"?
现在  是字面意思的"现在"吗
Yeah.
是的
Right...now.
现在
Just do it.
动手吧
Okay.
好吧
No!
不
Everybody settle down!
大家都别动
We need to get Benjamin back to the Kingdom.
我们得把本杰明带回神之国
Give the man his damn stick!
把那人的棍子还他
Get in the truck! Don't say a goddamn word!
滚回车里去  一个字都别说
- We need to get back. ?- No.
-我们得回去  -不行
Right now, you have to listen.
现在  你们都得听好了
For once, be present and listen.
就这一次  给我听仔细了
You will make your deliveries on time,
以后  你们必须每一次
every time, and they will be complete.
都按时送货  不能少一分
It's A's or F's, no I's.
要么优秀要么不及格  没有未完成
You are gonna show me that you understand
明天把你们欠的贡品送过来
by bringing the balance of what you owe tomorrow.
向我证明你们懂我的意思了
We need to go! He's bleeding out!
我们得马上走  他会流血身亡的
One cantaloupe, not more, not less!
一颗甜瓜  不多不少
Do you understand?!
明白了吗
Yes, I understand.
明白了
- Go patch him up. - Okay.
-去处理他的伤口吧  -好
Dianne, we need to drive to Carol's!
戴安  我们得带他去卡萝尔那里
We loaded her up with medical supplies!
我们给了她很多医疗用品
We need to stop the bleeding.
得赶快止住他的血
He's not gonna make it to the Kingdom.
他撑不到回神之国了
Let's go!
走吧
Up!
上来
Get in!
上车啊
Stay with me. Stay with me.
坚持住  坚持住
I'm right here. Stay with me.
我就在这  坚持住
- All right. Okay. - It's okay.
-好了  没事  -没事的
It's okay.
没事的
"T-To injure an opponent...
"伤害敌人
is to injure yourself.
就是伤害自己"
I'm sorry for coming to you.
很抱歉过来打搅你
We had no choice.
我们实在没办法了
Morgan, wait.
摩根  等等
Okay.
好了
Oh, God.
天啊
Stay away from me.
别靠近我
Just listen.
听着就好
No! No! Aah!
不  不
I know!
我知道
No! No! No!
不  不  不
Enough! No!
够了  不
Benjamin, get your gun up.
本杰明  把枪端起来
It was supposed to be me.
本来死的人该是我
That's what Gavin said --
加文说过
that I'd be first.
我会是第一个
I was trying to stop it.
我本想阻止的
I was gonna give my life to show you!
我本想献出自己的性命来警醒你们
That's what should've happened today.
今天本该那样的
That's what I tried.
我是那样试着做的
And something else happened
但是发生了意料之外的事
because we have done nothing to stop them.
因为我们没有做什么去阻止他们
We've done nothing!
我们什么都没做
Nothing.
没做
I was in a camp when it started.
灾变发生时我在一个营地
It was huge...endless...
无边无际的大营
a city of -- of tarps and latrines
到处是帐篷  茅厕
and wood smoke and babies crying.
炊烟  婴儿的哭声
There were always babies crying.
总有婴儿的哭声
I knew they had problems,
我知道情况不妙
but I didn't think they were mine to solve.
但我不觉得轮得到我来管
I thought there were stronger or smarter people there than me.
我以为比我有能力比我聪明的人会管
W-Who the hell am I, right?
我算什么呢
So I did nothing.
所以我什么都没做
A-And there was a fight...
之后有一场战斗
and a fire.
起了火
And I lost my wife.
我失去了妻子
And after three days of running,
三天没有食物  没有睡觉
no food, and no sleep...
恐怖骇人的
of horror and terror...
逃命后
I lost my little girl.
我失去了女儿
Right in front of me...
就在我面前...
because I didn't do something.
因为我什么都没做
Because I waited.
因为我干等
Listen to me.
听我说
Please.
拜托
Just listen.
听着就好
We can use what's happened.
我们可以利用这事
We can show the Saviors that we get it.
我们可以向救世军表明我们吸取了教训
We understand what we need to do.
我们明白要做什么
We know how to go on.
我们知道怎么继续下去
And they need to believe us.
他们要相信我们
We have to do something to make them believe us.
我们必须得做点什么使他们相信
And then, when we gain their trust back...
等我们赢回他们的信任后
we kill them...
再杀了他们
end them.
一了百了
We join with Alexandria and the Hilltop,
我们加入亚历山大和山顶寨的同盟
and we crush them in one fell swoop.
一举歼灭他们
But this is it, Morgan.
但你得接受事实  摩根
You have...to...kill.
你必须要杀戮
Or else you might as well just kill yourself.
不然你还不如自杀
Someone had to die.
总得有人死
I tried to be the one. That didn't happen.
我曾想成为那个人  但没有成功
So I'll be the one to lead our army
所以我要成为领导我们的军队
to crush the Saviors -- destroy them.
去粉碎救世军的人  摧毁他们
Me.
我
I'll talk to Ezekiel.
我会和以西结说
I'll tell everyone what I did.
我会告诉所有人我做的事
And I'll live the rest of my life making up for it.
然后我会用余生去弥补
Did you tell him?
你告诉他了吗
Did you?
有吗
Not now.
现在不行
We'll talk about it when we get back.
我们回去再说
What is it?
什么事
It's better to talk about it when we get back, Your Majesty.
最好我们回去再说  陛下
We'll talk about it now.
现在就说
How's the kid?
那孩子怎么样
He's dead.
他死了
Start walking back now before I kill you.
在我杀了你之前快滚
You say one word or throw one look,
你多说一句  多瞟一眼
I'll kill you right here and now.
我就地杀了你
Go!
滚
Do you have it?
东西拿了吗
I just want to say we get it.
我只想说  我们明白了
We understand.
我们懂了
- Cease this! - Leave 'em be!
-住手  -别管
Morgan! Stop!
摩根  住手
Morgan!
摩根
He set it all up.
都是他搞的鬼
He blocked the road yesterday, made us late.
他昨天挡路  让我们迟到
It was all him.
都是他干的
And we had your offering when we left --
我们离开时  贡品还在
had it all.
全都在
He took one from the cargo, and he hid it --
他从里面拿走了一颗  藏了起来
when we stopped.
在我们停车时
He wanted to get something started between the Kingdom and the Saviors.
他想挑起神之国和救世军的争端
Wanted to show you...
我想让你看到...
Wanted to show you that we get it...
我想让你看到我们吸取了教训
That we understand what it is that we need to do --
我们明白要做什么
that we know how to go on.
我们知道怎么继续下去
Good.
很好
Next week, same time.
下周  同一时间
We -- We understand.
我们明白
He -- He did this?
是他干的
He wanted to die for us before.
他之前就想为我们死
He wanted it to be him.
他希望死的是自己
Thought he could choose, and that's why Duane had to die.
他以为自己有的选  所以德韦恩才死了
"Duane"?
"德韦恩"
Benjamin -- Benjamin -- That's why Benjamin...
本杰明  所以本杰明才...
Morgan...
摩根
let us take our leave.
我们走吧
I was supposed to.
我本来就打算走
Morgan, you should not be alone here.
摩根  你不能一个人待在外面
Go.
走吧
Not now.
现在不行
- Benjamin not -- would not - ?Man, I said not now!
-本杰明不想...  -我说了现在不行
I said...
我说了...
Y'all just go.
你们走吧
Do you really want to know what happened in Alexandria?
你真想知道亚历山大发生了什么吗
What happened to you?
你怎么了
Killed Richard.
我杀了理查德
I strangled him.
掐死了他
He's the one got Benjamin killed, so...
他害死了本杰明  所以...
Do you want to know what happened in Alexandria?
你想知道亚历山大发生了什么吗
Yeah.
想
Negan killed Glenn and Abraham.
尼根杀了格伦和亚伯拉罕
What?
什么
Beat them to death with a baseball bat.
用棒球棍活活打死了他们
Now the Saviors have Alexandria, and Rick and everybody else...
现在救世军统治着亚历山大  瑞克和其他人...
everything they do is for the Saviors now.
都得为救世军做事
And they killed more.
他们还杀了更多人
Killed Spencer, Olivia...
杀了斯宾塞  奥利维亚
Jesus brought Rick and the rest here because...
耶稣带瑞克一伙人来是因为
Rick wants to fight them.
瑞克想反抗他们
You wanted to know.
是你想知道的
Now you do.
现在你知道了
- Where are you going? - I'm gonna kill them --
-你去哪  -我去杀他们
out there, one by one.
在外面  一个个杀
- But where? ? - Somewhere else.
-但是去哪  -别的地方
W-Wait.
等等
You can go...and not go.
你可以走  同时也不走
Please.
拜托了
Carol.
卡萝尔
I'm sorry.
我很遗憾
I thank you.
谢谢
I'm gonna be here now.
我会住在这里
We have to get ready.
我们要做准备
We have to fight.
我们必须反抗
We do.
是的
But not today.
但不在今天
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
原创翻译  双语字幕
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
最新连载海外影视剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com 仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利